www.linkedin.com/in/vzottmann

Victor Zottmann

www.github.com/victorzottmann

Frontend Developer

victor@victorzottmann.com

www.victorzottmann.com

SUMMARY

Dedicated frontend developer with 1.5 years of practical experience gained through internships. With a keen eye for design, Victor seeks to acquire further frontend skills to enhance interactions and elevate user experiences through innovative approaches.

SKILLS

Technical Skills:

- Proficient: JavaScript, React, Node.js, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Git
- Familiar: TypeScript, Bash, PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Unit Testing, Jira, Confluence

Soft Skills:

Teamwork, Positive Attitude, Problem Solving, Strong Communication, Strong Work Ethic, Critical Thinking

EMPLOYMENT

Engineering Intern Audinate Dec 2022 - Feb 2023

- · Streamlined development processes by successfully replacing a deprecated API responsible for file storage management within the company's database system using React, MongoDB, and Node.js.
- Wrote unit tests in the Mocha testing framework to ensure data integrity when uploading and downloading files.

Engineering Intern Audinate Mar 2022 - Sep 2022

- Enhanced an internal customer support platform by integrating multi-language support using the React Intl and React Context APIs with TypeScript.
- · Designed wireframes to aid engineers in improving the usability of the customer support platform.
- Helped product owners and managers refine customer requirements by developing practical user stories.

Research and Development Intern

Audinate

- In collaboration with an external client, participated in comprehensive testing of a proprietary desktop application, ensuring its smooth and successful release to market.
- · Played an integral role in the design thinking process and wireframe prototyping of a new product, contributing valuable insights to its development.

EDUCATION

Sydney, NSW

University of Technology Sydney

Feb 2022 - Dec 2023

Master of Interaction Design (Extension) - GPA: 6.44 / 7

· Major: Interaction Programming

Awards: Dean's List Engineering 2023

RECENT PROJECTS

Personal Website: www.victorzottmann.com (for additional information and projects)

Car Rental System (Website: https://victorz-car-rental.netlify.app/)

- Developed a website using HTML, CSS and JavaScript that allows users to rent cars on display.
- Utilized: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, AJAX, Local Storage, Bootstrap.

Arduino Memory Game (Demo: https://youtu.be/zJscLV0aoM8)

- · Built a physical prototype of a memory game using Arduino and electronic components.
- · Tested the product with real users to improve upon usability issues found in the first design iteration.
- Utilized: Arduino, C++, Soldering Tools.